http://www.trappist.net/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
HomeDirectionsContact Us
Main menu
Plan Your VisitDay VisitsGroup VisitsVisitor CenterAbbey ChurchRetreatsSchedulesArabia Mountain Heritage AreaAboutCommunityHistoryLay CisterciansPhoto GalleryContact UsJoin UsTo Be a MonkThe CallDiscernmentFormationMonastic Guest ProgramRecommended ReadingsQuestions and AnswersSupportPrayVolunteerDonateAbbey TradesMonks' BakeryStained GlassConservation Burial GroundOnline StoreAbbey Garden CenterNews & EventsMonastery NewsHomiliesUpcoming Events
You are herePrivacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve our website: we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from youTo process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on 9/1/2010
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by using this page.
©2020 Monastery of the Holy Spirit | All Rights Reserved
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
